

QA TESTER

PERSONAL DETAILS

I am 38 years young From Rishon LeTsiyon , Israel Automation developer in both Python and C#, Manual QA tester and Graduate of full stack .Net developer in Sela. A

team player with excellent technical skills and knowledgeable in many fields of science and technology.
Responsible, Diligent with a quick learning curve. Looking for position as a junior developer junior DevOps ,manual or automation tester

INTRESTS



FIND ME AT:

052-6633509



Rishon LeTsiyon , Israel



ehudsuryano@gmail.com



LinkedIn: @ehud-suryano

EHUD

SURYANO

WORK EXPERIENCE

QA ENGINEER

CLOUDINGNOW / NESS TECHNOLOGIES | 2023 - PRESENT

- Developing infrastructure and framework for automation testing using selenium and C#
- Developing automation tests in C# with Selenium
- Manual testing of SaaS product for invoicing service
- Composing Test cases and scenarios using TestRail and performing them
- \bullet working with SQL Databases and writing complex SQL queries to manipulate said databases
- · Logging and managing bugs and defects using Jira
- Using Postman to test API endpoints and requests/responds
- working in Scrum environment and Scrum rituals

TEST ENGINEER

WESTERN DIGITAL | 2019 - 2023

- Supervising execution of automated tests for firmware code of different flash memory products
- Failure analysis of tests logs
- Logging and managing bugs using Jira
- Managing a remote lab of stations and VMs
- Writing Powershell scripts to perform action on multiple stations at once in said lab
- Using Git version control system
- using Jenkins CI/CD
- · Manual testing of internal web based tools in development
- Composing STDs and STRs

QA AUTOMATION TESTER

DEVALORE | 2018 - 2019

- Developing automation tests in C#, Python with Selenium
- and BDD Behave
- Manual testing of software suits
- Composing STDs and STRs
- Logging and managing bugs using Jira
- Using Git version control system

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

FULL STACK .NET DEVELOPER

SELA TECHNOLOGY COLLEGE, 2017-2018

PRACTICAL ENGINEER -MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

TECHNOLOGICAL COLLEGE OF THE CORE OF ARMAMENT IDF 2004-2005

S K I L L S C# .NET Python Selenium Azrue cloud SQL

LANGUAGES

HEBREW

ENGLISH
(VERBAL, READING AND WRITING)